{
    "Questions": {

        "Question1": {
            "Question": "What is the main character's name?",
            "Options": [
                "King Authur",
                "The Black Knight",
                "Galahad"
            ],
            "Answer": "King Authur"
        },

        "Question2": {
            "Question":"What does the French Taunter launch towards the Knights of The Round Table?",
            "Options": [
                "Animals",
                "Sticks",
                "The Holy Grail"
            ],
            "Answer": "Animals"
        },

        "Question3": {
            "Question": "What did the Knights of The Round Table use to defeat the Rabbit of Caerbannog?",
            "Options": [
                "Holy Hand Grenade",
                "The Holy Grail",
                "King Arthur's Mighty Sword"
            ],
            "Answer": "Holy Hand Grenade"
        },

        "Question4": {
            "Question": "How can you tell a witch is a witch?",
            "Options": [
                "They have a terrible nose",
                "They have green skin",
                "They weigh as much as a duck"
            ],
            "Answer": "They weigh as much as a duck"
        },

        "Question5": {
            "Question": "Who was the first to join King Aurthur's knights?",
            "Options": [
                "The wise Sir Bedevere",
                "The Knights who say Ni!",
                "Sir Galahad the Pure"

            ],
            "Answer": "The wise Sir Bedevere"
        },

        "Question6": {
            "Question": "What word cannot be said by the Knights who say Ni?",
            "Options": [
                "It",
                "King Arthur ",
                "Sir Galahad"

            ],
            "Answer": "It"

        },

        "Question7": {
            "Question": "Why did King Arthur leave Camelot?",
            "Options": [
                "He was kicked out",
                "Camelot is a silly place",
                "Everyone's horse suddenly died"

            ],
            "Answer": "Camelot is a silly place"

        },
        
        "Question8": {
            "Question": "What is Lancelot's favorite color?",
            "Options": [
                "Blue",
                "Red",
                "Black"

            ],
            "Answer": "Blue"


    },

         "Question9": {
            "Question": "How does the Black Knight respond to getting his arms cut off?",
            "Options": [
                "You've unhanded me!",
                "My stance does not falter!",
                "Tis but a scratch!"

            ],
            "Answer": "Tis but a scratch!"


    },

        "Question10": {
            "Question": "Why does Sir Galahad miss out on a good time at Castle Anthrax?",
            "Options": [
                "The girls inside are evil",
                "He finds the grail",
                "He is rescued by the Knights"

            ],
            "Answer": "He is rescued by the Knights"


}

}
}